(Priya:)Morning.
(exhales)
- Sleep okay?
- Um uh.  Great!
(Leonard:)Hey, can I ask you something?
(Priya:)Sure.
(Leonard:)Last night, me wanting to try
that stuff out of the Kama Sutra.
(Leonard:)Was that fun for you
or kinda racially insensitive?
Yes. Just because you're in bed
with an India woman
(Priya:)you think that gives you permission
(Priya:)to use crazy positions
from an ancient Indian love manual.
(Leonard:)Hey, if you can find a book
called "Weird Sex with White Boys"
(Leonard:)I'd be okay with that.
(laughing)
No, no, you know you have such
beautiful eyes.
(Priya:)Have you ever thought about
getting contacts?
(Leonard:)I tried in the seventh grade.
I could never get used to them.
(Priya:)Oh. That's too bad.
(Leonard:)Yeah. If I had contacts,
I would have been the coolest
(Leonard:)Debate Club president ever to be
stuffed into his own cello case.
(Priya:)If you had them on now, you could
see what we're going to do next.